Jacob Landstrom

5201 W Donges Ln Brown Deer, WI, 53223 (920) 400-0338 jake.landstrom@gmail.com

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Adaptable professional with 9+ years of experience and a proven knowledge of full-stack development, distributed system design, database design, application and web design, and external application interfacing via REST, GraphQL, and EDI. Aiming to leverage my skills to successfully fill the software developer role at your company.

TECHNOLOGICAL EXPERIENCE

C# | .NET Azure | AWS S.O.L.I.D. Programming Principles ASP.NET Core MVC | Blazor | Razor Pages Azure DevOps | Github **Test-first Programming** Entity Framework Core Database-first & Code-first ORM Design Microsoft Identity Platform Python Microservice Architecture | Distributed Systems LINO | Expression Trees Javascript | JOuery Domain-Driven Design | Eventual Consistency HTML5 & CSS3 SQL Server Event Bus | Outbox Pattern

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Geneva10 Fulfillment Inc.

Delavan, WI

Sr .Net Developer

July 2020 – current

- Inherited and expanded API integration services for 3rd party eComm platforms
 - Integrated on-site warehouse management system to Shopify, WooCommerce and Reverb via RESTful and GraphQL APIs
- Lead developer for new warehouse management system
 - Designed and implemented backend database structure and APIs following a microservice architecture approach utilizing domain-driven design, inter-service messaging via event bus, and distributed data atomicity via eventual consistency
 - Created tool library for API consumers to support a de-coupled project structure
 - Created and implemented secure token service to centralize protection of APIs
 - o Wrote functional specifications for mobile applications and desktop UI pages to be used by front-end developers
 - Reviewed pull requests by development team
 - o Managed deployment of services to local VM and Azure for testing and production
 - Assisted junior developers with implementing microservice architecture patterns by building and running through PoCs
- Development tools used: C# / .NET, ASP.NET Core MVC & Blazor, EF Core / Dapper, MS Identity, SQL Server, HTML5 / CSS3, Javascript / JQuery, Azure Service Bus / RabbitMQ, Docker

Cascio Music Inc.

New Berlin, WI

Software Developer, eCommerce

Sep 2018 - Mar 2020

- Designed and developed in-house tools for Direct-To-Consumer and Amazon Direct (1P) use
 - o Live Price Tracking via multi-channel web scraper
 - o Azure Blob Image Downloader and Formatter via C# & MS Azure API
 - o DTC Inventory Report Generator via embedded VBA script for Excel
- Assisted management of e-commerce technology stack
- Lead migration of legacy db system to cloud storage platform
- Development tools used: Python, Java, VBA, C# / .NET

Sendik's Food Market Milwaukee, WI

eCommerce Associate

Aug 2015 - Sep 2018

- Create javascript tools utilizing Google AppsScript API to aid with large Google Sheets catalogs/projects
- Coordinate with Sendik's pricing and art departments to keep rotating items and categories updated
- Communicate with dev team at third-party cataloging platform for various projects
- Development tools used: Javascript, VBA

Minnesota Supercomputing Institute

Minneapolis, MN

Student Software Developer Apr 2013 – May 2014

- Assisted in development for MSI's biomedical tool suite, Galaxy
- Created wrappers to add new/updated tools to Galaxy platform
- Aided in the organization and completion of customer support tickets
- Development tools used: Java, Javascript, PHP, XML, HTML, CSS

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF MINNESOTA TWIN CITIES

Minneapolis, MN

B.A. Computer Science (May 2015)

REFERENCES

References available upon request